<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on HKUST Tech Club</title>
    <link>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on HKUST Tech Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 09:47:12 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hkusttech.github.io/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#8: Social Night at China Garden</title>
      <link>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/eighth-second-social-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 09:47:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/eighth-second-social-night/</guid>
      <description>Date and Venue The eighth meeting was held on 2018-04-20 at 7pm. The meeting venue was China Garden (G/F). It was the second social night of HKUST Tech Club.
Summary Oh hey there! Last Friday night&amp;rsquo;s dinner at China Garden was fun - we talked about Entrepreneur First, hackUST, startups, life.. oh and Markus&amp;rsquo; super cool dirty air detector - well just catching up in general! Ended it off with a nice family photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#7: Panel Discussion (Hack for Hackathons)</title>
      <link>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/seventh-meeting-hack-for-hackathons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 09:47:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/seventh-meeting-hack-for-hackathons/</guid>
      <description>Date and Venue The seventh meeting - Panel Discussion (Hack for Hackathons) was held on 2018-04-13 at 7pm. The meeting venue was CSE lounge and it is located at lift 25-26, 3rd floor.
Summary Thank you so much to everyone who came to the meetup last Friday! And huge applause to our wonderful panelists:
 Peter Chung Kenta Iwasaki Felicia Agatha Isaac Zachary To 李婷婷  We got some meaningful insights about how to gain most out of hackathons and learnt about some of the winning strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#6: The First Social Night</title>
      <link>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/sixth-meeting-first-social-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 09:47:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/sixth-meeting-first-social-night/</guid>
      <description>Date and Venue The sixth meeting was successfully be held on 2018-04-06 at 7pm. The social night was organized in HKUST Unibar
Summary First Social Night was FUN! Had a great time talking about aspirations and simply catching up with what everyone’s doing! We’re going to have social nights to meetup over dinner maybe once every two weeks from now on!
Event photos:
What is next? This Friday, we will have a “hackathon-themed” Meeting (cuz hackUST is coming up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#5: Blockchain and its application in FinTech and Insurance</title>
      <link>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/fifth-meeting-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 09:47:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/fifth-meeting-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>Date and Venue The fifth meeting was successfully be held on 2018-03-25 at 7pm. The meeting venue was CSE lounge and it is located at lift 25-26, 3rd floor.
Summary Last Friday we were honored to have Professor Paul Schulte to share with us his research and views on Blockchain and its current application in Fintech and Insurance. The interactive discussions we had revolved around: how blockchain can break down cartels, which cartels are utilizing this technology to maintain their position, what blockchain technology revolution is needed to truly build a decentralized system to benefit those who are cut off&amp;hellip;etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#4: How to Build a Smart Contract in 30 minutes?</title>
      <link>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/forth-meeting-smart-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 09:47:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/forth-meeting-smart-contract/</guid>
      <description>Date and Venue The forth meeting was successfully be held on 2018-03-18 at 7pm. The meeting venue was CSE lounge and it is located at lift 25-26, 3rd floor.
Summary Thanks for coming to our 4th Tech Club Meeting - special thanks to Jeff and 李婷婷 for giving an interactive workshop on &amp;ldquo;How to Build a Smart Contract in 30 minutes&amp;rdquo;
We also played MENSA games prior the workshop and Codigame afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#3: KiCAD workshop &#43; Coding game</title>
      <link>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/third-meeting-pcb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 09:47:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/third-meeting-pcb/</guid>
      <description>Date and Venue The event was scheduled from 7 - 9PM at Rm 2466 on 09-Mar-2018.
 Part 1: KiCAD workshop by Markus Part 2: Coding game session  Summary Thank you everyone who came to our 3rd workshop last Friday. And huge applause to our amazing presenter Markus for giving us a thorough demonstration of how to use KiCAD. Anyone who is interested in KiCAD and would like to know more, please contact Markus!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#2: React workshop</title>
      <link>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/second-meeting-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 09:47:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/second-meeting-react/</guid>
      <description>Date and Venue React workshop by lovely Christine and hang out. The event was scheduled from 7 - 8PM at Rm 2466
Summary Session #2 on React where Christine went through the front end &amp;amp; backend of a project (more info of the session will be posted on slack)
What is next? Next week we will have Markus to provide an introduction to the KiCad EDA from 7 - 8 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1: HKUST Tech Club First Meeting</title>
      <link>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/first-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 09:47:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkusttech.github.io/events/first-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Date and Venue The first meeting was successfully be held on 2018-02-24 at 7pm. The meeting venue was CSE lounge and it is located at lift 25-26, 3rd floor.
Summary Thank you so much for coming to our first meeting. It was exciting to witness the level of interest all of you have, in technology first hand.
We have decided to create 4 groups: Data visualization, React, algorithms , Decentralised systems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>